orcd.co 2019-06-10

# Privacy – Help Center

Effective June 7 2018

Your Privacy is our priority. Feature.fm believes in contributing to build a more transparent and trustworthy web experience for a better and more personalized internet moving ahead.

These summary points are designed to provide information on Feature.fm's practices around data collection and does not substitute our full Privacy Policy. Please review our full Privacy Policy below for more details.

**_Information we collect_**

Browser, device, OS, IP-Derived Location, conversion details in case of a purchase, visit specific events such as bounce or music previews, release specific parameters such as Artist, Album, Track, etc.

We collect email address, first name, last name only after End Users opt-in and consent to providing this information to us. Additionally, End Users will receive emails or other targeted messages from us and/or the Customers only after they opt-in for the same. End Users may opt out of receiving messages at any time and can review all PII data being stored by Feature.fm and request for it to be deleted.

End Users may also opt-in to sharing additional personal information from third party social and music services such as Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Deezer, Spotify, Apple Music, and other similar apps, as well as to provide us with information such as likes, favorites, followers/following, follower numbers, age, top artists, top tracks, playlists and/or music listening behaviors.

Feature.fm Customers who sign up to the Service with an account will also provide personally identifiable information including first name, last name, and email address upon sign up. 

**Basis for processing your personal information**

Processing your Personal Information is necessary for the performance of the Terms and the provision of the Services to you. Processing the information for marketing purposes is based upon your consent. Processing for the purposes of developing and enhancing new features and our products and services, for analytics and usage analysis, for fraud prevention and security and for our recordkeeping and protection of our legal rights – are all necessary for the purposes of legitimate interests that we pursue.

**_How Feature.fm uses data_**

Feature.fm collects data about online activities in the in any of Feature.fm's Sites and/or Services for the below purposes:

  * To provide statistics and insights.
  * To allow our Pixel Partners to provide advertising about products and services tailored to individual consumers’ interests.
  * To provide advertising tailored to End Users’ interests through Feature.fm's owned advertising products
  * To allow our Customers, such as the artists, labels, and music marketers (data controllers), to send emails, messages, and other communications tailored to End Users ' interests.
  * To administer and provide services to Feature.fm's Customers.

**_How Feature.fm collects data_**

**_Cookies and similar technologies_**

We use cookies and similar technologies to help personalize your experience. You can adjust your settings to determine which cookies you do or do not allow. Changing your settings and/or deleting existing cookies may affect the Services _or your experience of the Site/s **.**_

**_Directly_**

Feature.fm Customers who sign up to the Feature.fm Suite Services will directly provide information for Feature.fm to administer Services.

End Users may also choose to provide information directly to Feature.fm and its Customers through the Services and/or Third Party Services.

**_Connecting_** **third party services**

End Users may opt-in to sharing additional Personal Information from third party social and music services such as Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Deezer, Spotify, Apple Music, and other similar apps.

**_From advertising publishers_**

In certain advertising products such as sponsored songs, Feature.fm's publishing and streaming partners share non-identifiable information about how End Users interact with its advertising products. All partners that share data with Feature.fm must be in compliance with this Privacy Notice and retain a privacy policy that is in accordance with applicable laws.

**_Opt-Out_**

You can easily opt-out of interest based advertising facilitated by Feature.fm at any time by managing your permission settings when you visit any Feature.fm Sites and/or Services. This opt-out will prevent advertisers from receiving any data about the opted-out visitors.

**_Transferring data internationally_**

The data you provide to us may be transferred or accessed on a global basis where Feature.fm's Customers, partners, affiliates, or data processors are located to countries where data protection laws may differ from those in the originating country. Please see our full Privacy Notice below for more information.

**_Data that Feature.fm will not accept_**

Feature.fm does not knowingly collect data or information from children under the age of thirteen (13), or if they are EU citizens, the age of sixteen (16).

**_Your right to be forgotten_**

You have a right to access, update and/or delete your Personal Information and obtain a copy of the Personal Information that Data Controllers have collected about you. You can change your mind at any time about your election to receive marketing communications from us and/or having your Personal Information processed for direct marketing purposes.

To access, update, or delete your Personal Information where Feature.fm is the Data Controller, please email [privacy@feature.fm](mailto:privacy@feature.fm).

To access, update, or delete your Personal Information where Feature.fm is the Data Processor, please contact the Data Controller from whom you received a communication or email from.

**_Retention_** **.** We retain information for as long as necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Notice. 

**_Security_** **.** We implement industry standard measures aimed at reducing the risks of damage and unauthorized access or use of Personal Information, but they do not provide absolute information security.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**. We may change this Privacy Notice from time and shall notify you of such changes.

We at ListnPlay Ltd. d/b/a Feature.FM (“ **Feature.FM** ” “ **us** ”, “ **we** ”, or “ **our** ”) recognize and respect the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers. If not otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms have the meaning given to them in the Terms of Service, available at ffm.to/terms (the “ **Terms** ”). This Privacy Notice describes the types of information we collect from you when you visit our website as well as the landing pages that we create for our Customers (as defined below) and/or use our Services (respectively, the “ **Site/s** ” and ” **Services** ”). This Privacy Notice also explains how we may process, transfer, store and disclose the information collected, as well as your ability to control certain uses of the collected information.

ListnPlay Ltd. is the data controller in respect of some of the processing activities outlined in this Privacy Notice. Our registered office is Dubnov 7 St, Tel Aviv-Yafo, Israel 6473207 and our registration number 514676311.

There are various ways in which we provide our Services. We partner with artists, agents and/or record labels in the music industry (the “ **Customer** ”) in order to enable them to promote their music. Sometimes, we may provide our Services in white-label format for the use of our partners (the “ **White Label Customers** ”), in which case the White Label Customers will receive the same information as we and/or our Customers do under this Privacy Notice. Our Services can be provided by means of, in conjunction or partnership with third party sites, applications or services, such as Music Smart Links, streaming services, social media accounts or musical websites, or can be integrated into the Customers’ landing pages (together with the uses made by the White Label Customers, the “ **Third Party Services** ”). We collect certain information from our partners, such as the Customers, as well as certain information from end users of the Services and/or Third Party Services (“ **End Users** ”).

This Privacy Notice applies only to the collection and use of information by Feature.FM, and not to the collection and use of information by partners, Customers and Third Party Services. Please refer to the privacy notices of the partners, Customers and Third Party Services to understand their privacy practices. Partners, Customers and Third Party Services may collect and/or use your information in different ways than we do, and we are not responsible for any actions of partners, Customers and/or Third Party Services.

“ **Personal Information** ” means any information that refers, is related to, or is associated with an identified or identifiable individual or as otherwise may be defined by applicable law. 

**_Information We Collect_**

We collect information from you when you choose to use our Site/s and/or Services. In order to use our Site/s and/or Services, you will be required to register and provide us with certain Personal Information. We also collect Personal Information when you make use of the Site/s and/or Services, request information from us, sign up for newsletters or our email lists, complete online forms, or contact us for any other reason. If you use the Services by logging in through streaming service accounts (such as Spotify or Deezer) or other social media account, we may also receive Personal Information about you as provided by streaming or social accounts,. Please check such third-party’s policies in order to understand what information we receive.

Examples of the Information that we collect from Customers or from End Users may include your name, IP address, IP-derived location, device ID, e-mail address, browser, operating system, conversion details in case of a purchase, visit specific events such as bounce or music previews, release specific parameters (such as Artist, Album, Track), likes, favorites, followers/following, follower numbers, age, top artists, top tracks, playlists and/or music listening behaviors, profile, location and date of birth. Such Personal Information may be collected by us through the Site/s and/or Services.

We also collect your browsing history on the Site/s and/or Services.

In addition, when you use the Site/s and/or Services, certain information may be automatically gathered about your computer or mobile device, such as operating system, IP address, and subject to your consent as may be required under applicable law, (geo) location, as well as your browsing history and any information regarding your viewing on our Site/s and/or Services.

It is your voluntary decision whether to provide us with any such Personal Information, but if you refuse to provide such information we may not be able to register you to the Site/s and/or Services and/or provide you with the Services.

**_How We Use Your Personal Information_**

_General_

We and any of our trusted third-party subcontractors and service providers may use the Personal Information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to provide you with the Site/s and/or Services; (2) to respond to your inquiries or requests, contact and communicate with you; (3) to develop new products or services and conduct analyses to improve our current content, products, and services; (4) to provide you with customized content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Site/s and/or Services, on other third-party sites or apps you may visit, or via e-mail; (5) for us or our Customers to contact you with informational newsletters and promotional materials relating to our Site/s and Services; (6) to review the usage and operations of our Site/s and Services; (7) to use your data in an aggregated, non-specific format for analytical purposes (as detailed below); (8) to prevent fraud, protect the security of our Site/s and Services, and address any problems with the Site/s and/or Services and (9) to provide customer support. 

_Statistical Information_

By analyzing all information we receive, including all information concerning users, we may compile statistical information across a variety of platforms and users (“ **Statistical Information** ”). Statistical Information helps understand trends and Customer-needs so that new products and services can be considered and so existing products and services can be tailored to Customer desires. Statistical Information is anonymous and aggregated. Statistical Information which has not been linked to any Personal Information may be shared with our partners, without restriction, on commercial terms that we can determine in our sole discretion. Certain Statistical Information that is linked to Personal Information may be shared (a) with the relevant Customers and (b) made be shared with other end users of Third Party Services in accordance with the privacy policies of those Third Party Services.

_Analytics_

We, or our service providers or subcontractors, may use analytics tools (“ **Tools** ”), including “Google Analytics” to collect information about the use of the Site/s and/or Services. Such Tools collect information such as how often users visit the Site/s and/or Services, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites and mobile applications they used prior to visiting the Site/s and/or Services. The Tools may collect certain Personal Information, and may link such Personal Information to specific information stored in our database. We use the information we get from the Tools to improve our Sites and Services. Google's ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Sites is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use located at <http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html> and the Google Privacy Policy located at <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>.

_Legal uses_

We may use your Personal Information as required or permitted by any applicable law.

**_Disclosure of Information_**

We may share your information, including Personal Information, as follows:

_Business Partners, Service Providers, Affiliates, and Subcontractors_

We may disclose information, including Personal Information we collect from and/or about you, to our trusted service providers, business partners, affiliates, subcontractors, who may use such information to: (1) help us provide you with the Site/s and/or Services; (2) aid in their understanding of how users are using our Site/s and Services; (3) when you have consented to such disclosure, provide to you targeted offers and advertising on both our Site/s and/or Services, as well as on other apps/platform/sites you choose to visit. Such retargeting may be performed by our partners and/or White Label Customers. 

Personal Information that we collect and process on behalf of Customers and/or White Label Customers as data controllers will be shared with such Customers and/or White Label Customers. Please note that sometimes the White Label Customers will be acting as Data Processors on behalf of third-party controllers, which controllers will also receive the applicable Personal Information.

_International Transfer_

We may use subcontractors and service providers and have Customers, business partners and affiliates who are located in countries other than your own and send them information we receive (including Personal Information). We will ensure that these third parties will be subject to written agreements ensuring the same level of privacy and data protection as set forth in this Privacy Notice. You hereby consent to such international transfer.

_Business Transfers_

We may transfer our databases containing your Personal Information if we sell our business or part of it, including in cases of liquidation. Information about our users, including Personal Information, may be disclosed as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets or acquisition and shall continue being subject to the provisions of this Privacy Notice.

_Law Enforcement Related Disclosure_

We will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity, behavior or (digital) content and information of or related to an individual, including in the event of any user suspected to have engaged in illegal or infringing behavior. We may also share your Personal Information with third parties: (i) if we believe in good faith that disclosure is appropriate to protect our rights, property or safety (including the enforcement of the Terms and this Privacy Notice); (ii) to protect the rights, property or safety of third parties; (iii) when required by law, regulation subpoena, court order or other law enforcement related issues; or (iv) as is necessary to comply with any legal and/or regulatory obligation. You can request such Personal Information as specified herein by emailing us at privacy@feature.fm.

_Other Uses or Transfer of Your Information_

We allow you to use our Site/s and Services in connection with third-party services, sites, and/or mobile applications, such as the Third Party Services. If you use our Site/s and/or Services with or through such third-parties, we may receive information (including Personal Information) about you from those third parties. Please note that when you use third-parties outside of our Site/s and/or Services, their own terms and privacy policies will govern your use of those services.

**_How We Protect Information_**

We make efforts to follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**_How to Access and Limit Our Use of Certain Information_**  

You have certain rights in relation to the Personal Information that we hold about you, as detailed below. We reserve the right to ask for reasonable evidence to verify your identity before we provide you with any information and/or comply with any of your requests, as detailed below. Some of these requests will be directed to the relevant data controllers:

ï    **Right of Access and Data Portability.** You have a right to know what Personal Information we collect about you and, in some cases, to have the information communicated to you. Subject to the limitations in applicable law, you may be entitled to obtain from us a copy of the Personal Information you provided to us (excluding information that we obtained from other sources) in a structured, commonly-used, and machine-readable format, and you may have the right to (request that we) transmit such Personal Information to another party. If you wish to exercise this right please contact us at privacy@feature.fm letting us know what information in particular you would like to receive and/or transmit. Please note that we may not be able to provide you with all the information you request, for instance, if the information includes Personal Information about another person. Where we are not able to provide you with information that you have asked for, we will endeavor to explain to you why. We will try to respond to any request for a right of access as soon as possible.

ï    **Right to Correct Personal Information.** Subject to the limitations in applicable law, you may request that we update, correct or delete inaccurate or outdated Personal Information and/or that we suspend the use of Personal Information, the accuracy of which you may contest, while we verify the status of that Personal Information. We will correct your Personal Information within a reasonable time from the receipt of your written request thereof.

ï    **Deletion of Personal Information.** In certain circumstances you have a right to have Personal Information that we hold about you deleted. Should you wish to have any Personal Information about you deleted, please contact us at privacy@feature.fm. Subject to applicable law, we will delete Personal Information provided to us by a user within a reasonable time from the receipt of a written (including via email) request by such user to delete such collected Personal Information. We cannot restore information once it has been deleted. Please note that to ensure that we do not collect any further Personal Information, you should also terminate your account with us and clear our cookies from any device where you have used our Services. We may retain certain Personal Information (including following your request to delete) for audit and record-keeping purposes, as well as other purposes, all as permissible and/or required under applicable law. We may also retain your information in an anonymized form.

ï    **Account Deactivation.** Customers can ask us to deactivate their account by contacting us using the information below and/or by accessing their account settings at https://account.feature.fm/account/profile and clicking “Delete my account”. In order to deactivate your account, we may ask you for additional information.

ï    **Direct Marketing Opt Out.** You can change your mind at any time about your election to receive marketing communications from us and/or having your Personal Information processed for direct marketing purposes. If you do, please notify us by contacting us as detailed in this Privacy Notice. We will process your request as soon as reasonably possible, however it may take a few days for us to update our records before any opt out is effective.

ï    **Right to Object.** Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to object to processing of your Personal Information including for the purpose of direct marketing.

ï    **Supervisory Authority**. If you are a European Citizen, you may have the right to submit a complaint to the relevant supervisory data protection authority.

ï    If you are a California resident, you may request certain information once per year about our disclosure of certain categories of Personal Information during the preceding calendar year to third parties for such third parties’ own direct marketing purposes. Please send your request by email [privacy@feature.fm](mailto:privacy@feature.fm), or by postal mail to Feature.fm, 85 Broad Street, Suite 17.089, New York, NY 10004. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the email or mailing addresses specified in this section.

**_Data Retention_**

Subject to applicable law, we retain information as necessary for the purposes set forth above. We may delete information from our systems, without notice to you, once we deem it is no longer necessary for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Notice.

**_Cookies and Similar Technologies_**

ListnPlay Ltd. uses cookies and similar technologies to help personalize your experience and to personalize the ads we serve you. A “persistent” cookie may be used to help save your settings and customizations across visits. Third parties through which we provide the Services and/or our business partners may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information in the course of advertising being served on different websites.

**Functional cookies** \- When you visit our Site/s, we place a functional cookie on your device that helps us provide insights on your activities on our Site/s, including how your device has interacted with the Site/s. Functional cookies are instrumental to the functionality of the service and expire after 10 minutes

**Performance cookies** \- When you visit a Site, we may also place a performance cookie on your device. Performance cookies differ from functional cookies as they can exist on the user’s device for an extended period of time until expired or until they are deleted. These cookies are used to store and remember a user’s preferences such as the preferred music service or to detect recurring visits to the Site/s.

**Third-Party Advertising cookies** \- When you visit our Site/s, we also places third-party advertising cookies on your device, which help our partners deliver or enable the delivery of advertising that is customized to your interests and to keeps track of how many ads users have seen.

Advertisers on mobile devices may use advertising (or ad) identifiers (non-permanent, non-personal device identifiers such as the Android advertising ID and/or Apple's ID for advertising, or IDFA) to enable and optimize their advertising. You can reset these identifiers or indicate your preference that they should not be used for advertising purposes, as detailed below.

_How to Adjust Your Preferences_

Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but you can change this setting so your browser either refuses all cookies or informs you when a cookie is being sent. In addition, you are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. We also provide a way for End Users to accept and change their cookie preferences directly on Feature.fm’s pages. Please note that some features of the Sites and/or Services may function improperly when cookies are disabled or removed. 

By changing your device settings, you can prevent your device's ad identifier being used for interest-based advertising, or you can reset your device's ad identifier. Typically, you can find the ad identifier settings under “privacy” or “ads” in your device's settings, although settings may vary from device to device. 

Adjusting your preferences as described in this section does not mean you will no longer receive advertisements, it only means the advertisement you do see will be less relevant to your interests.

**_Third-Party Applications and Services_**

All use of third-party applications or services (including Third Party Services) is at your own risk and subject to such third party's privacy policies.

**_Communications_**

Subject to your consent and applicable law, we may send you e-mail or other messages about us or our Services. You may remove your Personal Information from our and/or our Customers’ and/or our White Label Customers’ mailing list and stop receiving future communication from us by following the UNSUBSCRIBE link located at the bottom of each communication or by emailing us at [privacy@feature.fm](mailto:privacy@feature.fm) or the Customers/White Label Customers at their email addresses. Please note that we reserve the right to send you service-related communications, including service announcements and administrative messages relating to your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them. Should you not wish to receive such communications you may cancel your account.

**_Children_**

We do not knowingly collect personally-identifiable information from children under the age of sixteen (16). In the event that you become aware that an individual under the age of sixteen (16) has enrolled without parental permission, please advise us immediately.

**_Changes_**

When visiting this Site/s and/or using our Services, you shall be asked to accept the terms of this Privacy Notice. If you do not agree with the terms hereof, please do not use the Site/s and/or Services. We may update this Privacy Notice from time to time – we encourage you to review it periodically. By continuing to access or use the Site/s and/or Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised privacy notice; if we have your email we will notify you of such changes. We will post the updated Privacy Notice on this page. Please come back to this page periodically to make sure you are familiar with the latest version. Any new Privacy Notice will be effective from the date it is accepted by you.

**_Comments and Questions_**

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, or if you wish for us to amend or delete your Personal Information, please contact us at [privacy@feature.fm](mailto:privacy@feature.fm).
